Guide to the Actors' Equity Association Records WAG.011
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series VI: Claims
  - Barnard, Harold, Producer Doctor Social v. AEA members Dean Jagger (original signature) and Al Shean, 1948 (Box 271, Folder 13)
  - Barnes-Carruthers Theatrical Enterprises v. Johnny Desmond and AEA: failure by Desmond to perform terms and conditions of contract, 1965-1967 (Box 271, Folder 14)
  - Barnhart, Lyle B. v. James H. Hendrickson: transportation claim, 1929 (Box 271, Folder 15)
  - Baron, Henry: salary claims on various productions, 1925-1933 (Box 271, Folder 16)
  - Barr, Richard: use of LORT/Stock contract pre-Broadway, 1968 (Box 271, Folder 17)
  - Barrett, Edith v. Ann Seranne Her Cardboard Lover: salary claim, 1938 (Box 271, Folder 18)
  - Barrett, Sheila: commission payments on Thumb's Up, 1934-1935 (Box 271, Folder 19)
  - Barrymore, Elaine Barrie v. M.D.C. Corporation and Richard Myers My Dear Children: salary claim, 1939-1940 (Box 271, Folder 20)
  - Barrymore, Ethel (original signature): salary and expense claims against her for An Amazing Career, 1933-1941 (Box 271, Folder 21)
  - Barrymore, John Drew: suspension, 1954 (Box 271, Folder 22)
  - Barrymore, John Drew v. Ralph Bellamy as President of AEA: suspension from 1954, 1957-1958 (Box 271, Folder 23)
  - Barton, James: conduct charges brought by members of the Tobacco Road Company, 1939 (Box 271, Folder 24)
  - Barton, Virginia v. Jane Winslow, Monomoy Theatre: transportation claim, 1942 (Box 271, Folder 25)
  - Batchelor, Walter, Inc. v. The Locust Sisters: salary claim, 1927 (Box 271, Folder 26)
  - Baxter, George v. Edgar Levy, Yardley Theatre: salary claim, 1947 (Box 271, Folder 27)
  - Baxter, George v. M.G. Michaels Antonia: stolen costume claim, 1926 (Box 271, Folder 28)
  - Baxter, Gladys v. Select Operation Corporation and J. J. Shubert Three Waltzes: salary claim, 1938 (Box 271, Folder 29)
  - Baxter, Gladys v. Shubert Theatre: salary claim, 1929-1931 (Box 271, Folder 30)
  - Bayes, Nora: various cases including Julius Tanner v. Nora Bayes, 1921 (Box 271, Folder 31)
  - Beau Brummel Company cast members' v. Arnold Daly: salary claims, 1916-1918 (Box 271, Folder 32)
  - Behavior of Mrs. Crane Company: salary claims, 1928 (Box 271, Folder 33)
  - Bekefi, Maria v. Miss Lillian Albertson, Desert Song, Los Angeles: contract violation, undated (Box 271, Folder 34)
  - Bentham, M.S. v. Murvyn Vye: commission claim, 1945-1946 (Box 271, Folder 35)
  - Bergen Players and S. E. Stanton: salary claims, 1928-1929 (Box 271, Folder 36)
  - Berkeley, Busby Players: salary claims, 1928 (Box 271, Folder 37)
  - Berryman, Anne: Being "miscast", 1922 (Box 271, Folder 38)
  - Betty Dear Company: salary, railroad fares and money extended claims, 1926-1928 (Box 271, Folder 39)
  - Bickford, Charles (original documents and signatures) v. James W. Elliott Underworld: salary claims, 1928 (Box 271, Folder 40)
  - Big Boy Company: overtime claims and other contract issues, 1924-1926 (Box 271, Folder 41)
  - Bijou Players, Savannah, Georgia: salary claims, 1927 (Box 271, Folder 42)
  - Birch, Wyrley v. Elmo Productions and/or Elsa Moses: salary claim Touch T' Chaw, 1937-1939 (Box 271, Folder 43)
  - Black Crook Company: salary claim, 1934 (Box 271, Folder 44)
  - Blackbirds(Lew Leslie's Blackbirds of 1939): salary claim, 1938 (Box 271, Folder 45)
  - Blackmer, Sidney v. A. L. Jones and Morris Green Social Register: salary claim, 1932 (Box 271, Folder 46)
  - Blau, Bela, Deertrees Theatre The Guardsman v. Miriam Hopkins: breach of contract, 1940 (Box 272, Folder 1)
  - Blind Alleys Company: salary claims, 1924 (Box 272, Folder 2)
  - Blonde Sinner Company: salary claims, 1926 (Box 272, Folder 3)
  - Blonde Sinner Company v. Harry Short: performing while intoxicated, 1926 (Box 272, Folder 4)
  - Blondell, Joan: engagement at the Avondale Playhouse, 1964-1965 (Box 272, Folder 5)
  - Blood, Adele et al v. Dixon Amusement Company Abie the Agent: salary claims, 1920-1921 (Box 272, Folder 6)
  - Blum, Daniel Bambina Company v. Frederick Graham: breaking a contract, 1930 (Box 272, Folder 7)
  - Blunkall, John, Equity Representative to WPA Federal Theatre Project: letters for and against him including signed letter from Hallie Flanagan, 1936 (Box 272, Folder 8)
  - Boland, Joseph v. Roger Quinlan What a Woman Wants: salary and transportation claims, 1929 (Box 272, Folder 9)
  - Bolger, Ray (original signature) v. On Your Toes, Inc. and Dwight Deere Wiman: termination rider, 1936-1937 (Box 272, Folder 10)
  - Bolger, Ray v. George White: termination of contract, 1932 (Box 272, Folder 11)
  - Bononova, Fortunio v. Minnie Elizabeth Webster: personal representative agreement, 1930-1931 (Box 272, Folder 12)
  - Bond, Raymond: appearing non-Equity in his play Kitty Dooley of Times Square, 1935 (Box 272, Folder 13)
  - Boston Opera House Stock Company: salary claims, 1943 (Box 272, Folder 14)
  - Bowman, Patricia v. Lew Brown Calling All Stars: salary claim, 1934 (Box 272, Folder 15)
  - Box Seats Company: salary claims, 1928 (Box 272, Folder 16)
  - Boyle, Billy v. Select Operating Corporation and Lee Shubert: salary claim Hellzapoppin, 1942-1943 (Box 272, Folder 17)
  - Boylston, Augusta v. Lucille La Verne: salary claim, 1929 (Box 272, Folder 18)
  - Bradbury, Walter v. Shubert Theatrical Company: salary claim, 1925 (Box 272, Folder 19)
  - Brady, William A. v. Mrs. Patrick Campbell (original signatures): salary claim, 1933-1934 (Box 272, Folder 20)
  - Brady, William A. v. Helen Hayes: contract dispute, 1927 (Box 272, Folder 21)
  - Brandt's Subway Express Company: salary claims, 1931 (Box 272, Folder 22)
  - Brass Ankles Company: salary claim (found in Strong Stuff file), [1931] (Box 272, Folder 23)
  - Brice, Fanny (original signature) v. Select Theatres Corporation, Lee Shubert: salary claim, 1934 (Box 272, Folder 24)
  - Bridegroom Company v. Joseph Shay: salary claims, 1924 (Box 272, Folder 25)
  - Bridge of Distances Company: salary claims, 1925 (Box 272, Folder 26)
  - Brilliant, Saul v. Vincent Youmans, Inc.: salary claim, 1929 (Box 272, Folder 27)
  - Brisson, Carl v. Richard Kollmar [and vice versa] Early to Bed: breach of contract, 1943 (Box 272, Folder 28)
  - Broad Street Theatre Company, Newark, NJ: salary claims, 1933 (Box 272, Folder 29)
  - Broadway Players, Chattanooga, Tennessee: security, 1927 (Box 272, Folder 30)
  - Broadway Players, Hempstead, Long Island, NY: salary claims, 1935 (Box 272, Folder 31)
  - Broadway Players, Patchogue, Long Island, NY: salary claims, 1929 (Box 272, Folder 32)
  - Broadway Players, Williamsport, PA: salary claims, 1929 (Box 272, Folder 33)
  - Broadway Players, Woodcliffe, NJ: salary claims, 1939 (Box 272, Folder 34)
  - Broderick, Lillian v. Florenz Ziegfeld, Jr.: breach of contract, 1921 (Box 272, Folder 35)
  - Broken Chain Company: salary claims (includes J. Carrol Naish original signature), 1929 (Box 272, Folder 36)
  - Brother Elks Company: salary claims, 1926 (Box 272, Folder 37)
  - Brown, Chamberlain v. William Harrigan: commission claim, 1931-1933 (Box 272, Folder 38)
  - Brown, Chamberlain v. Martin Jurrow, Alan Holmes and others: various issues, 1941 (Box 272, Folder 39)
  - Brown, Chamberlain v. Pauline Lord: commission on For Five Thousand Dollars(includes transcript of hearing), 1925 (Box 272, Folder 40)
  - Brown, Chamberlain v. John Marston: failure to pay commission, 1928-1932 (Box 272, Folder 41)
  - Brown, Chamberlain v. Jack Marvin: breach of personal representative agreement, 1931-1932 (Box 272, Folder 42)
  - Brown, Chamberlain v. Ralph Morgan, Albert West, Harold Bolton, Carl Frank, William Harrigan: various arbitrations and fees for arbitrations, 1933-1937 (Box 272, Folder 43)
  - Brown, Chamberlain v. Herbert Rawlinson: commission owed, 1930-1933 (Box 272, Folder 44)
  - Brown, Chamberlain v. Lysle Talbot: breach of personal representative's contract, 1931-1932 (Box 272, Folder 45)
  - Brown, Chamberlain Players: salary claims, 1936 (Box 272, Folder 46)
  - Brown, Clarence v. Ione Smith: Brief for Defendant-Appellant, 1921 (Box 272, Folder 47)
  - Brown, Elmer, et al v. Pee-Bee-Gee Production Company and Paul Blaufox: expense claims, 1938 (Box 272, Folder 48)
  - Brown, Elmer v. Jack Yellen and Lou Holtz You Said It Company: salary claims, 1930-1931 (Box 272, Folder 49)
  - Brown, Richard Chester (Jeff) v. Francis I. Curtis: religious discrimination/dismissed for being Jewish, 1947-1948 (Box 272, Folder 50)
  - Bryant, Dorothy as Executive Secretary of Chorus Equity Association (CEA) as assignee for Marion Anderson et al: salary claims for They All Do It Company, 1927 (Box 272, Folder 51)
  - Bryant, Dorothy as Executive Secretary of Chorus Equity Association (CEA) as assignee of the Chorus of Thanks A Lot v. Frank Barnum, Bob K. London, Producers and Mrs. Jennie Bernstein, Guarantor: salary claims, 1932 (Box 272, Folder 52)
  - Bryant, Lester: salary claim, 1927 (Box 272, Folder 53)
  - Bryant, Nana v. Shubert Theatre Corporation The Circus Princess: salary claim, 1927 (Box 272, Folder 54)
  - Buckaroo Company: salary claims, 1929 (Box 272, Folder 55)
  - Buckner Review, Arthur Buckner: various claims, 1921-1922 (Box 272, Folder 56)
  - Bulls, Bears & Asses: salary claims, 1932 (Box 272, Folder 57)
  - Bunk of 1926 Company: salary claims (Box 272, Folder 58)
  - Burgess Players v. Jack Roseleigh: salary claims, 1923 (Box 272, Folder 59)
  - Burke, Tom v. Bohemians, Inc.: salary claims, 1924 (Box 272, Folder 60)
  - Burn Your Head, Jack Productions, Inc.: salary claims, 1927 (Box 272, Folder 61)
  - Burnett, Carol and Burngood, Inc. v. On-Stage Productions, Fade-Out-Fade In and Management of Fade-Out-Fade In, Inc. v. Carol Burnett: AEA Special Committee Meeting Transcript, Nov 12, 1964 (Box 272, Folder 62)
  - Burnett, Carol and Burngood, Inc. v. On-Stage Productions, Fade-Out-Fade In and Management of Fade-Out-Fade In, Inc. v. Carol Burnett: Answer of Carol Burnett to charges, Oct 8, 1964 (Box 272, Folder 63)
  - Burnett, Carol and Burngood, Inc. v. On-Stage Productions, Fade-Out-Fade In and Management of Fade-Out-Fade In, Inc. v. Carol Burnett: Arbitration materials, Nov 1964 (Box 273, Folder 1)
  - Burnett, Carol and Burngood, Inc. v. On-Stage Productions, Fade-Out-Fade In and Management of Fade-Out-Fade In, Inc. v. Carol Burnett: Arbitration materials, Dec 1964-Feb 1965 (Box 273, Folder 2)
  - Burnett, Carol and Burngood, Inc. v. On-Stage Productions, Fade-Out-Fade In and Management of Fade-Out-Fade In, Inc. v. Carol Burnett: Hearing of Charges of Management Transcript, Dec 3, 1964 (Box 273, Folder 3)
  - Burnett, Carol and Burngood, Inc. v. On-Stage Productions, Fade-Out-Fade In and Management of Fade-Out-Fade In, Inc. v. Carol Burnett: Hearing of Charges of Management Transcript, Dec 18, 1964 (Box 273, Folder 4)
  - Burrough, Tom v. Harry M. Warner (original signature): salary claim, 1919 (Box 273, Folder 5)
  - Butt, M. Lawton v. Silvio Hein: salary claim, 1920-1921 (Box 273, Folder 6)
  - Butterfly Girl: salary claim, 1925 (Box 273, Folder 7)
  - Bye, Bye, Barbara Company: salary claims, 1924-1931 (Box 273, Folder 8)
  - Bye, Bye, Bonnie Company: salary claims, 1927-1928 (Box 273, Folder 9)
  - Byers, Nancy as producer Isn't It So: salary claims, 1923-1924 (Box 273, Folder 10)
  - Cabaret: additional payments to chorus, 1966-1967 (Box 273, Folder 11)
  - Café de Danse and Gregory Ratoff: salary claims, 1929-1933 (Box 273, Folder 12)
  - Cahill, Lily v. Oliver D. Bailey and Nathan Smith A Stitch in Time: salary claim, 1918 (Box 273, Folder 13)
  - Cain, Gerogia v. Same H. Harris Theatrical Enterprises: salary claim, 1932 (Box 273, Folder 14)
  - Calhern, Louis and Leo G. Carroll (original signatures) v. Eddie Dowling Agatha Calling: salary claims, 1935-1937 (Box 273, Folder 15)
  - Call Me Madam: chorus dressing room conditions, 1951 (Box 273, Folder 16)
  - Call of Duty: sale to the movies, 1956 (Box 273, Folder 17)
  - Cameo Girls: salary claims, 1921 (Box 273, Folder 18)
  - Cameo Playhouse Theatre: contract and bonding problems, 1952 (Box 273, Folder 19)
  - Candlelight Company: deputy and dues issues, 1929 (Box 273, Folder 20)
  - Candlelight Company: salary and transportation claims (including William Frawley, original signature), 1930-1931 (Box 273, Folder 21)
  - Capehart, Charles v. Barry Townly, Inc.: repayment of promissory note, 1924 (Box 273, Folder 22)
  - Capital Theatre Stock Company, Albany, NY: salary claims, 1934-1936 (Box 273, Folder 23)
  - Captive Company: salary and other expense claims, 1933 (Box 273, Folder 24)
  - Carlyle, Grace v. John Mulvihill and Chamberlain Brown: breach of agreement, 1921-1924 (Box 273, Folder 25)
  - Carnival Company: salary and contractual claims, 1929 (Box 273, Folder 26)
  - Carroll, Earl Vanities v. Sam Liebert: salary claim on dismissal plus other salary claims (company includes Fifi D'Orsay, original signature), 1935-1936 (Box 273, Folder 27)
  - Carroll, Leo G. v. Charles L. Wagner Perfect Alibi: salary claims (original signatures), 1930 (Box 273, Folder 28)
  - Carry Nation Company: salary claims, 1932 (Box 273, Folder 29)
  - Casey Furni Stock Company: membership payment for Miss Joan Adams, 1923 (Box 273, Folder 30)
  - Casino de Paree, Inc.: salary claims, 1935 (Box 273, Folder 31)
  - Cass, Maurice v. Ben Stein, Inc. and Sidney Salkow and/or Irving Salkow: salary claims The Black Tower, 1931-1932 (Box 273, Folder 32)
  - Cast of The Russia v. Sanford E. Stanton: salary claims, 1929-1930 (Box 273, Folder 33)
  - Cast of Strange Interlude Company v. C. E. Wee: salary claims, 1930-1932 (Box 273, Folder 34)
  - Cast of Uninvited Guest Company v. Sam Gresman: salary claims, 1927-1934 (Box 273, Folder 35)
  - Castanets Company: salary claims (including Sydney Greenstreet, original signature), 1929 (Box 273, Folder 36)
  - Caubet, Susan v. Shubert Theatre Corporation Imported Wife: salary claim, 1925 (Box 273, Folder 37)
  - Cavanaugh, Hobart v. James W. Elliott Mr. Gold Digger: salary claim, 1931-1932 (Box 273, Folder 38)
  - Century Players, E. C. Waller, General Manager v. Sherrold Page: contract jumping, 1924 (Box 273, Folder 39)
  - Chalmers, Thomas v. Michael Todd (original signature) Hamlet: salary claim, 1945-1946 (Box 273, Folder 40)
  - Champagne and Tragic Eighteen companies: co-op payment, 1926 (Box 273, Folder 41)
  - Lytell, Bert as President of AEA v. Red Barn Theatre, Inc. and Stuart Chaney Here Today Company (including Ruth Gordon, original correspondence), 1940-1941 (Box 273, Folder 42)
  - Chaplin, Lita Grey (original signature): billing and wardrobe claims for The Little Racketeer, 1931-1932 (Box 273, Folder 43)
  - Chase, Ilka v. David Belasco (original signatures): salary claim, 1930-1932 (Box 273, Folder 44)
  - Chase, Ilka v. Jed Harris (original signatures): salary claim, 1932-1933 (Box 274, Folder 1)
  - Chatterbox Revue, Inc.: salary claims in lieu of notice, 1925 (Box 274, Folder 2)
  - Chatterton, Ruth as Treasurer of Actors' Fidelity League v. John Emerson as President of Actors' Equity Association (AEA), Managers' Protective Association (MPA) et al: briefs, memoranda and correspondence, 1924 (Box 274, Folder 3)
  - Chatterton, Ruth as Treasurer of Actors' Fidelity League v. John Emerson as President of AEA, MPA et al: Order to Show Cause, 1924 (Box 274, Folder 4)
  - Chauve Souris Company: salary claims, 1943 (Box 274, Folder 5)
  - Cherry Orchard Company, Westchester County Center: salary claims, 1931 (Box 274, Folder 6)
  - Chiffon Girl Company: salary claims, 1924-1930 (Box 274, Folder 7)
  - Chinese O'Neill Company: salary claims, 1927-1929 (Box 274, Folder 8)
  - Chippies Company: salary claims, 1929 (Box 274, Folder 9)
  - Chorus Equity Association (CEA) v. S. M. Chartock-Gilbert and Sullivan Company: salary claims, 1952-1953 (Box 274, Folder 10)
  - CEA v. Unity Amusement Company: salary claims, 1937 (Box 274, Folder 11)
  - CEA claims for extras who should be chorus, Rodgers and Hammerstein's King and I, 1951 (Box 274, Folder 12)
  - CEA for Make a Wish v. Jule Styne and Harry Rigby: salary claims, 1951 (Box 274, Folder 13)
  - CEA member Chauncey Reynolds v. Lew Cooper Run Little Chillun Company: transportation expense claim, 1943 (Box 274, Folder 14)
  - CEA members v. Joseph Kipness and High Button Shoes Company #2: travel claims, 1949 (Box 274, Folder 15)
  - CEA members v. M.W.W. Productions, Inc. and Meyer W. Weisgall Romance of a People: salary claims, 1934-1935 (Box 274, Folder 16)
  - CEA members v. Michael Todd (original signature) Something for the Boys: salary claim, 1942-1943 (Box 274, Folder 17)
  - CEA members Seventeen Company v. Sammy Lambert, Melton Berle and Bernie Foyer: salary claims, 1951-1952 (Box 274, Folder 18)
  - CEA on behalf of 33 members v. Lee Sabinson and Finian's Rainbow Company: transportation claims, 1950 (Box 274, Folder 19)
  - Christy, Orrin E., Jr. as Manager and Producer of The Glass Menagerie v. Actors' Equity Association (AEA): additional payments due James Ray and Nancy Pinkerton, 1965 (Box 274, Folder 20)
  - Chronicle House (Independent Art Theatre), Cleveland, Ohio: contract with Egon Brecher, 1923 (Box 274, Folder 21)
  - Cisney, Marcella and Michael: charges from 1949 on the West Coast, 1950-1951 (Box 274, Folder 22)
  - Civic Center Stock Company, Rip Van Winkle: salary claims, 1974 (Box 274, Folder 23)
  - Clayton, Frederic, Producer of the Colonial Players at Norfolk, Virginia: member claims, 1933, 1942 (Box 274, Folder 24)
  - Cleaves, Robert v. Dirk Harvey, Lyla Graham, David Mauro, Elizabeth Rogers, Jeremy West: behavior while members of Actors Theatre Company, Los Angeles, CA, 1966-1967 (Box 274, Folder 25)
  - Clemant-Walsh Players: salary, transportation and expense claims, 1930-1940 (Box 274, Folder 26)
  - Clive Players, Copley Theatre, Boston, Massachusetts v. Marshall Vincent: Vincent absent from performance charges, 1929 (Box 274, Folder 27)
  - Clutching Claw Company: salary claims, 1928 (Box 274, Folder 28)
  - Coastwise Annie Company: salary claim by Shirley Booth (original signature), 1932 (Box 274, Folder 29)
  - Coastwise Trader Company: salary claims, 1930 (Box 274, Folder 30)
  - Cobb, Lee J. (original signature): Theatre Guild contract, The Fifth Column, 1940 (Box 274, Folder 31)
  - Cocktails 5 to 7 Company v. Select Theatre Corporation: salary claims, 1942 (Box 274, Folder 32)
  - Community Chautauqua Potash Company: transportation claims, 1923-1925 (Box 274, Folder 33)
  - Cooper Square Players: salary claims, 1925-1928 (Box 274, Folder 34)
  - Colbert, Claudette: claim for dress from Leah Kleshner Company, 1924 (Box 274, Folder 35)
  - Colbert, Claudette (original signature) v. Al H. Woods: breach of contract, 1927 (Box 274, Folder 36)
  - Cole, Toby v. AEA/Zero Mostel: claim for agency commission Fiddler on the Roof, 1964-1967 (Box 274, Folder 37)
  - Collier, Constance v. Actors Theatre, Inc. John: transportation claim, 1927-1928 (Box 274, Folder 38)
  - Collier, Constance (original signature) v. Edwin H. Knopf A Spot on the Sun: salary claim, 1928 (Box 274, Folder 39)
  - Collins, Ray v. Willman, Inc. Native Son: claim for stolen wardrobe, 1941 (Box 274, Folder 40)
  - Collision Company: salary claims, 1932 (Box 274, Folder 41)
  - Colonel Players Stock Company, Utica, New York: salary, transportation and expense claims, 1931-1933 (Box 274, Folder 42)
  - Colonial Stock Company, Baltimore, Maryland: various claims against "Max" Thomaschevsky and Max Cohen, 1923 (Box 274, Folder 43)
  - Colt, Ethel Barrymore (original signature): salary claim, George White Scandals, 1931 (Box 274, Folder 44)
  - Come on Ruth a.k.a. Solid Ivory: claims against bond, 1926-1933 (Box 274, Folder 45)
  - Comedy of Women Company: salary claims, 1929 (Box 275, Folder 1)
  - Comes the Revelation Company: salary claims (includes Will Geer and Audra Lindley, original signatures), 1942, 1946 (Box 275, Folder 2)
  - Concord Hotel, Appropriate Unit: representation, 1969 (Box 275, Folder 3)
  - Conlan, Frank: salary claim for Snatchaway Girl, 1935 (Box 275, Folder 4)
  - Connolly, Walter (husband of Nedda Harrigan): tax return (Form 1040), 1928 (Box 275, Folder 5)
  - Convoy, Frank v. Herman Shumlin: contract jumping, The Little Foxes, 1938-1939 (Box 275, Folder 6)
  - Constant Sinner Company: salary claims, 1931-1943 (Box 275, Folder 7)
  - Conway, Alban and Jennifer Dante v. Cameron Matthews (Repertory Company): salary claims, 1932-1933 (Box 275, Folder 8)
  - Cook, Don v. Chamberlain Brown: commission, 1930-1932 (Box 275, Folder 9)
  - Cook, Joe v. Vanities Producing Corporation, Earl Carroll, President: breach of contract, 1924 (Box 275, Folder 10)
  - Cooper, Frank Associates Agency v. Arnold Stang; commission and expense claims, 1965-1966 (Box 275, Folder 11)
  - Cooper Square Players: salary claims, 1926 (Box 275, Folder 12)
  - Corio, Ann (original signature) v. Jules Pfeiffer: salary and other claims, 1946 (Box 275, Folder 13)
  - Corio, Rafael: I Killed the Count contract start problem, 1942 (Box 275, Folder 14)
  - Cornell, Elmer v. Chamberlain Brown: commission claims, 1931-1932 (Box 275, Folder 15)
  - Cos-Hay Corporation operating Montclair Theatre: creditors claims, 1945-1946 (Box 275, Folder 16)
  - Cosden, Robert: transportation and salary claims for Uncle Tom's Cabin, 1946 (Box 275, Folder 17)
  - Cotsworth, Staats v. WH Corporation, Stewart Chaney, President: salary claim, 1939 (Box 275, Folder 18)
  - Cotton, Joseph (original signature) v. Jack Curtis Born in a Trunk: salary claim, 1937 (Box 275, Folder 19)
  - Council of Resident Stock Theatres (CORST) v. Actors' Equity Association (AEA): service charge on health insurance coverage, 1965 (Box 275, Folder 20)
  - Countess Maritza Company: salary claims, 1928 (Box 275, Folder 21)
  - Cowles, Albert v. Marconel Corporation and Marc Connelly (original signature): salary claim, 1937 (Box 275, Folder 22)
  - Cradle Snatchers Company: salary claims, 1932 (Box 275, Folder 23)
  - Crazy with the Heat Company: salary claims, 1940-1941 (Box 275, Folder 24)
  - Criminal Code Company v. George Sharp: salary claims, 1930 (Box 275, Folder 25)
  - Crippo, Kernan: dismissal from the Park Players and hiring by Manchester Amusement Company, 1922 (Box 275, Folder 26)
  - Cronyn, Hume (original signature) v. Mr. Big Company: salary claim, 1941 (Box 275, Folder 27)
  - Crooks Convention Company: salary claims, 1929 (Box 275, Folder 28)
  - Cutler, Ben v. Cheryl Crawford and John Wildberg One Touch of Venus Company: run-of-play salary claim, 1944-1945 (Box 275, Folder 29)
  - D. M. Productions, Inc. v. Elizabeth Austin Kerr: breach of contract, 1965 (Box 275, Folder 30)
  - D. M. Productions, Inc. v. Elizabeth Austin Kerr: breach of contract/hearing transcript, Jun 1965 (Box 275, Folder 31)
  - Dale, Bert and Pagie v. My Golden Girl, Inc.: salary claim, 1921 (Box 275, Folder 32)
  - Dale, Esther v. Gifford Cochran Three Penny Opera: salary claim, 1933 (Box 275, Folder 33)
  - Dale, Gypsy v. Henry Jewett: salary, transportation, expense claims, 1921 (Box 275, Folder 34)
  - Dale, James v. Chanin Productions, Inc. Solitaire Man: contract length, 1927-1929 (Box 275, Folder 35)
  - Dalton, Doris v. Select Theatres Corporation Blow Ye Winds: reimbursement claim for stolen items, 1937 (Box 275, Folder 36)
  - Daly, Arnold v. Joseph E. Shea On the Stairs: salary claim, 1922-1923 (Box 275, Folder 37)
  - Dalzell, Paul, Charles W. Meyer, Arthur Aylesworth, Florence Weber v. Boris Said Dew Drop Inn: salary claims, 1917-1920 (Box 275, Folder 38)
  - Damita, Lily: alien actress for The Playhouse, Providence, Rhode Island, 1942 (Box 275, Folder 39)
  - Dangerous Maids, Edgar MacGregor, Producer: salary claims, 1921-1943 (Box 275, Folder 40)
  - Daniel, Mary Players: salary claims, 1927 (Box 275, Folder 41)
  - Darling, Dorothy v. Paper Mill Playhouse, Inc.: salary claim, 1939 (Box 275, Folder 42)